So hello good morning and welcome back once again
everyone welcome to ICICI Lomb
Brokers Premier League season two and two six
season three we got first semi final semi
finalist
the team Howden second quarter final here we go all in
readiness
Pink Panthers taking up against Anand Rath
United three to one game on
and that's got away nicely bye straight to the
fielder
no run straight to the fielder so here we are the two
batsmen Atul Sharma Piyush Lodha and Prateek
Kadam already started the presidings
from Pink Panthers
second quarter final
direct hit could be the chance
that's good running and also there was a very
good throw from the fielder covers but
single check four ball three runs no wicket
wow
excellent shot that will go all the way for four
runs
captain
need to come back
what a first fantastic game we had
quarter final one that was between Howden
vs United strikers they one by one run
what a match
so dot ball two one go on seven for no loss
Anand Rath United
and  This time flicked nicely for a single
run at mid wicket
1.18 for no loss
Rahul Sawant bowling the second over inside
I has lucky
and pushed it lightly for a single run
1.29 for no loss.  There could have been a
direct
hit opportunity here and a wicket could have been taken.
Both batsmen rotating the strike here, the
score is now in double digits 10 runs
1.310 runs No wicket
down the track but completely beaten
looking to play across the line Piyush Lodha
10 balls 10 phnoo loss that's a
good strike but only a single run.
So very good from Rahul Sawant, just
considered for runs.  Seven runs came in the first over
now four runs came in 1.51 runs no wicket
and that's a good strike
just a single
Anand Ra United
so two was gone 12 for ola quarter final
two
and we had a fantastic Anand Ra
United supporters so Anand Ra United
supporters make some noise
kya baat hai wow and if you are supporting
Pink Panthers makes some noise
they say sare players andar hai
but may be spectators watching they are
supporting
and waiting for the more crowd to become to watch this
exciting game of cricket the
quarter finals one the iconic cricket
ground in Mumbai Fatima Grounds we
got the one semi final team howdun
qualified.
The total four quarter final games today.
Semi-final one, semi-final two and it will be the
one match for third place and then the grand
finale.
So many more entertainment to come stay tuned
to watch ICI Lumbar Brokers Premier League
Live on YouTube channel Go Live.  So like
and subscribe and press the bell icon to
get the regular updates of the match.   That's
played away nicely for a single.
Piyush and Atul rotating strike for
singles.  Piyush has got one boundary in the
first over.
13 No loss oh that's gone what a
Sami
this time he has lifted the ball in the air one bounce
fielder is present there in the cow corner
region and will take two runs one
on 15 Akash Jadhav is a fast batsman.
He batted brilliantly last season
and batted brilliantly yesterday too.
Lots of big hits and today there's a
chance in the air for the team this time and great effort
there.
If Glenn Phillips had taken this catch, it would have been the
best catch and I think Glenn
Phillips would have definitely taken a flight from there and
come here.  What a spectacular effort by
the fielder.
Almost fielders became goalkeepers.
He dived, jumped and swam.
What was that?  And One More Chance This Time
in the Air and He Takes It.  That's
how Howrah won the match and
now the second quarter final, there is a
different excitement in this Fatima
Grounds.
Yes Mitesh,
God is also a little kind today.
Sunlight has not yet reached the ground.
Due to which the dues have not been cleared.
And due to dew, the ball is coming with a little pause.
Three overs, 17 runs, two wickets.
Now Atul will take the strike.   He is a
very good and composed batsman.   The
cover drive is his pattern shot.   Yes, you are
absolutely right.  I faced some difficulties here in the beginning.  There is a
little dew factor and now we have to see that as the
game progresses here,
some sunlight will come here and we are looking for sunlight,
some ground will be maintained, yes as a
new bowler, Hemant
left arm over the wicket, I will have to
bat with some understanding
which is the target in your mind set.  We will have to reach that
goal.
Then you will be able to depend.  The next ball was
pushed lightly to the on side.
Vikas is the fielder behind.
Vikas is also considered a good fielder.   He is
bowling very well.
Three balls, two runs.
Three balls, two balls, 18 for three,
a little change in fielding,
Yash, we have to do some fireworks here, Fire
Vaux, we have to bat aggressively now,
signal for a wide ball,
Umpires Tajmal Khan, Leg umpire Naushad Khan, the
next ball was a good ball and it went over the
outside edge, the keeper was collected by the third man, could
not stop it for one run,
Deepesh and Nitesh Kumar, the batsmen are at the crease
and the
last over was very good, Vikas Shukla,
one over, five runs, two wickets and now
look here, three runs and one wicket in three balls,
excellent bowling,
this time he has sent the ball in the air but the
ball could not reach the fielder, and two runs will be
taken here, the
left-handed batsman, Om Sir, feels that there is
a good opportunity to hit a six over long-on, yes, there is a little
boundary shot for him, it is a
boundary shot for the left-hander,
not a little more, two to four meters,
which can be crossed.   The
next ball was a
good,
yes, light ball.  The batsman could not read the
ball and it became a dot.
Reminds me of a left-handed batsman.   The
six Suresh Raina hit over
long on off Brett Lee in the 2011 World Cup semi-final was a unique moment.   Yes,
Suresh Raina was also a very strong batsman.
Pushed lightly towards square leg.  The
first run is strong and the second run is slow.  It
is very risky to see but
if there was a little weakness in the throw and a little force had been applied then the batsman could have got
into trouble.
Yes exactly the over ends with two runs
four overs 24 for three Anand Rathi United.
So Anand Ra United you have to say
United are you ready you have to say
United I will say Anand Rathi ok three
to one here we go Anand Rathi
Anand Rathi will win
brother will win
Om sir we will say both the teams will win and
whichever team wins, whichever team
plays good cricket,
whichever team wins will give us a party, yes
congratulations to him from our side,
batsman
four overs three for 24.  Now in the coming four overs,
Om Sir, it seems that this is a target and
now a bigger target will have to be set
for the Pink Panthers.   Yes, you will have to
take a little risk.   The
next ball was a very good ball but it
went slightly outside and umpire Naushad
opened both his arms and declared a wide ball.
New bowler Vikas
played a shot on the right arm and mid wicket from the pavilion. Two players
behind the ball will
not be able to stop the two runs.
One run shot. One run shot.
Umpire Naushad,
players, pay attention, you cannot escape the eyes of the umpire,
you will have to complete the run.
Next ball, a good ball from Vikas towards the pavilion, he
took the inside ball and ran towards third man for a
run.
Four balls, two runs, two fours, four overs, two balls, 27
runs, three wickets.
Next ball, Vikas has pulled to Deepesh.   The
first run was hit hard and there was some
effort from the players and they could not stop Deepesh from scoring two runs.
Next ball was a
shot to the heart Vikas
played with a little light hands
Four overs, four balls, 30 runs, three wickets Two balls remaining in this over Nitesh on
strike Vikas's next ball
was a ball lightly on the feet which he hit on the
leg side and took four runs, a very
good shot
Three wickets Last ball of this over was a
slow one for Nitesh
and once again the fielder made a mistake
and two runs
again Nitesh and Deepesh
Five overs, 36 runs,
three wickets Yes, we will have to
see in the coming three overs
Anand Raj United How will Nitesh Kumar and
Deepesh bat and
he says that he will
drink some water outside the pitch Nitesh Sir, the
umpire will pay a little attention outside the pitch
and for a while I got scared here
The way you have started, the
voice you have raised Very strict umpiring
Om Sir the energy is on
Yes Mitesh, with your support the energy remains intact throughout the
day
because I was also a big lover of cricket, I have
played a lot of matches before, so cricket is
my life in a way
and when I enter the ground,
I  There is no feeling of pain or discomfort during the day.
You have a great experience
and I would also like to tell the upcoming talents to
just practice cricket.
Practice well.  Play leather ball, tennis
ball when you have time and
enjoy the game here.  This time he has
played it cleverly.  Scooped it over the boundary line
for four runs.
He is also an innovative batsman and this is something amazing that can be
seen only in modern day cricket.
Yes, if Mitesh is a smart batsman then
he will play according to the fielding.
Player 1 is placed at square leg and
Deepesh is looking towards that side.  See
where you play.
Rahul's next ball,
Deepesh is ready.   It was a
good ball.  Coming out of good length.  The
keeper was also beaten.
One run as 22.
41 for three with this one bye.  The score of
Anand Raj United and Deepesh Nitesh Kumar we just
talking about looking for that fire
works they got one boundary and there will be the
big over coming up let's see
so Om sir the excitement will be double Saturday
started with day one and day two today
after the league match now there are eight teams and the quarter
final is second so it will be interesting and the
upcoming match will be very double interesting yes see you
all the matches will
be interesting because the same eight teams which have played well will
play today.   In the
last match of the first day,
seven runs were needed from one ball.   If
14 runs are needed in three balls, then the best
batting was done by
Mausam Mausamkar. The batsman is Sagar Mausamkar.
He hit a wonderful six and there was a
hope that seven runs were needed in one ball, he
hit another six but he could not connect.
Yes, he
wanted to play a reverse shot on the next ball but he was completely
beaten.
Very clever batting by Rahul.  He
saw that Deepesh had already turned around.
Bowled the ball further into the off side.  The ball came from a good length and landed
in the hands of the wicketkeeper
who was standing at square leg.
His shot there is blocked with a little bit of a heart scoot.
Two balls remaining in this over.   The
next ball was a good ball from Rahul's side of the pavilion, it was
on the off side but the
batsman ran for the second run and could
not complete it, Deepesh got run out, a
very strong throw came to the keeper and the keeper did
not make any mistake,
yes absolutely, here the fielder should have very
fast, quick reflexes
because every run is precious here.   Yes
Mitesh, but the throw should come at the right end.   It
is very important here to throw at the correct end.  But Deepesh batted well here.
He has hit a four.
Worked for my team.   Yes.
13 off 10 balls and 5.5
for 43.
Rahul Sawant will bowl the last ball of this over.   The
new batsman is
also not a left-handed batsman, sorry he
bats with his left hand and Neeraj bats with his right hand. The
last ball of this over was a
pitched ball by Rahul for Neeraj. He played a slightly short ball
towards third man and the player there
missed the ball but the player at point ran for
two runs.
So the over ends with two runs.
Four for 45 after six overs.  Who will win and
who will lose?  Attack.
12 balls remaining in this match.
Let's see what it looks like,
a 60 in 12 balls,
like in the first quarter final, the
team was chasing a target of 60, they got
shot by one run,
yes Nitesh,
I think a 70 score will be very
challenging,
yes, for that some big hits are
needed,
Pratik Kadam,
yesterday also he bowled very well, fielded very well, let's
see what he does for his team today.
Nitesh is on strike.
Good ball, tried to hit the overpitched ball hard on the on side
but it was a
slight miss.
Player positioned on the on side.
He will not get more than one run.
Now comes Neeraj, a very tall and strong
batsman.  Let's see what he does in front of Pratik.  The
next ball was
pushed lightly to the off side of Pratik.  The
batsman ran for one run.  Will complete the second run also.   The
score is 48 for 4 with two runs and
Neeraj and Nitesh are at the double N crease.
Now he would like both the batsmen to play till the end, if there is
no wicket then each one should get a big score of
65, 70 as you said, they must have hit big fours
and sixes, the way the
batting has been done here, the
bowling has been excellent, being Panthers,
yes Mitesh played with very light hands
towards square leg, there was a fielder there
and there was a fumble, the fielder took the first run with force, could
not stop it from two runs,
with two runs Anand Rai United completes 50 runs,
50 up
and this time good strike high in the air but it will
land safely between the two fielders, they will
go for two,
so you see, here they are rotating the strike from two runs.
Good batting is
happening here.  Anand R United
52 for four with
two balls remaining in this over.   Let's
see what Neeraj does in these two balls.
Pratik has bowled well so far but he did
not get much support from the fielders.
Where one run should have been scored,
two runs were scored.  Good running between the
wickets.  Played lightly towards third man,
last ball of this over,
four wickets for 53,
now on strike, Nitesh is known for hitting long shots.
As we said, hit with a little light hands.   The
batsman ran for one run and took the second run.
Neeraj is a very
tall and strong player.
And very good running between the wickets.  Seven
overs, 55 runs, four wickets.
Om,
let's see
how many points Nitesh and Neeraj can add to their team's tally in the last six balls?
55 for four after seven overs Anand Raj
United Coming up in the last over of the
first innings
Parasharam
in the bowling attack, there has been a
good partnership between these two
38 runs in 23 balls for five wickets,
excellent bowling this time, we have
seen a lot on this pitch, medium pacer and left arm
spin gets a good turn movement,
yes,
left arm
bowler has always proved to be effective.  If the
pitch is kept correct then it becomes a little difficult to play.
Next ball
and again a dot ball like Nitesh ji,
I told you that the angle formed by the left arm on the
off side beats the batsman again and again.
If he is a smart batsman, then if he
reads it, he can hit it well.
Third ball of this over
to Neeraj, two balls were dot. Third ball was a good
ball. Miss shot and the ball was spinning towards point.
One run.
Three balls were two runs in this over. Yes, we will have to
see the last three balls. Currently the score is 57 for four
and we will definitely go for three big hits.
Here Neeraj and Nitesh will
try their best
because a big
target will be set here. It is a big
contest, a quarter final game and
who will enter the semi final,
the way Parash Ram has bowled here
and this run out will have to be seen. The
leg keeper could not collect the ball.
I think he dropped the stump with his hands.  The
ball has not come into his hands.
Like here we had a vision that the ball was
not in his hand.  His hand is on the stump.  It
seems to me that the
umpire has given not out.
So with two runs the score here is 57 for four.   Will
check more.  Yes, here three extra
means wide and plus two.  Four last three balls at 60,
we were talking that we can reach 70
but good ball here in the block hole,
not giving any chance for a big shot,
yes Mitesh did not
come in his slot, otherwise he would have
sent it straight for six runs, yes
but a very good ball was bowled, it was a
block hole
yorker ball and Neeraj played it equally well.
Four on 61, last two balls and this time he plays it to the
long on area for two runs.  The
throw is direct and will be out.
Excellent throw:
Captain Hemant made an excellent throw there in the long on area.
And after the fifth wicket, it was
62 for five
and coming up on the last ball of the first
innings.
What would you like to say about that last ball six
wicket Om Sir.   Yes
, we have to see that there are new batsmen.   The
captain must have told him something before sending him.
What do you have to do on the last ball?
Very good bowling
left arm
and
missed the keeper is a little hurt here on
this short pitched ball
and that's gone 62 for six Pink
Panthers they need 63 to win
and now coming up for the toss time one more
quarter final admit Titans captain
and one il one team captain come for the toss so I
believe it's going to be a very-very
tough competition.
Whoever wins, it should start with us, right?  And
admit Titans Dheeraj you've been a fantastic
contender we've seen in other tournaments too.
And this is the big moment for you.
Would you like to enter the semi-finals by
beating them?
Obviously, the motive of every team is to play in the
finals.  And our
motive is also the same that we will play the finals and
definitely ICCI one IL team is a
very strong team.  We have seen the batting
line up, bowling line up yesterday.  So, we have
already made the strategy how
to defend.
We have not seen any video, friend.
Okay if you're a fan of one I'll one team make some
noise.   Come
on kids.
Ok.  If you are a fan of one I will one team
int counter three to one make some noise.
What is the matter.  The voices of all three of them have been heard.
And if you're a fan of Admit It, Titans
Make Some Noise.
Admit Titan won.
And from the official Who Will Call?  Admit
Titans Will Call Hades Is The Call Hades It Is
You Want The Dot What To Decided And
Why?  Bowling Bowling.
Okay, I wish you all the best.
So Adam Titans they have one the decided to
bowl first quarter final three will be the
biggest rivalry of the
tournament coming up
back in the match
so welcome back once again everyone who are
watching us live the present over here
myself Mish Solanki I welcome you all
ICS Lombard proudly presenting
Brokers Premier League two to six season 3
we are in Mumbai on a fantastic
environment here and currently Mumbai
witnessing 24 degree centigrade the
temperature is a bit rising now as in the
morning it was around 19 degree
centigrade
and we are all set to start the second
innings play Pink Panthers they need 63 to
win and who will enter into the semi-final we
already got the one semi-finalist the team whom they
defeated team you strikers
okay before the start mean while music
DJ
can welcome in a count of three to one game
on
first ball first ball oh that was a chance
for the catch  A bit of misjudgement
at the fielder standing at point that could be
the big wicket if that could be taken
to run out
Vishram Sakkare
on strike Pratik Kadam on strike
and Neeraj Bhardwaj
already started presiding
53 to chase, we have seen the first quarter
final.
The target was set up at 60.
So we are getting there number 60.  Again on the
scoreboard.
Wow innovation.  That's a scope.
But good stop.  Only a single.
And the umpires will do a little check here.
So that's not a boundary.   I
inform all the teams that it will be the nearest
person's call and the players' call.  We do
n't have a review system here.
Very good ball.  Very good effort on the off side.
But
excellent effort 100 marks for the effort
excellent effort
loud applause and once the
fielding was a bit there he lost his balance
and got four runs
10 runs in four balls no wicket Pink
Panthers have
blown the ball in the air there is a chance
and here the catch was missed and a dream was broken at
such a time a catch should have been taken here
but luck is on his side Pink Panthers
11 runs in five balls no wicket
this time wanted to play went to on side
there was a fielder on the off side he was a
bit late if he had run quickly then
a catch could have been taken 12 runs after one over
no wicket needed in seven overs 51 runs
music
and welcome once again Om Sir you are
in combox seven overs 51 I think
Pink Panthers will bat like this in the coming three overs
12 runs per over then they will chase the target easily
Yes Mitesh Mishra Ram is
batting very well and
along with him Prateek Kadam is considered a good batsman.  I want to
see that Akash is a
good left arm round across bowler.
Able to take out the next ball of the sky.   The
first ball of the sky.
Very good ball.
Tried to play on the on side but
took a slight outside edge towards cover.
No runs.  Like I said, Akash is a
good bowler.
Next ball from Akash.  A very good ball,
looking low and
easily caught by the fielder but the
fielder did not support Akash.
Now rest is on strike.
Next ball, good ball from Akash to Vishram
and he will not let go of it again.
Vishram again wants to play his favourite shot
but
those who have made the batsman uncontrollable,
a 50 at 1.43, now wants to connect in 38 balls.
Very rarely have we seen players
in tennis cricket who connect well on the
leg side, they just wait for the shot to come up
pitch length again
and he can hit a big shot,
wanted to take the second one.
14 for 1 after two overs and 49 needed from six overs.
49 runs in six overs.  The
current run rate is from and required
around 8.17
Eight runs in every over will win this match
for Team Pink Panthers
Quarter final two is on
and once again welcome to everyone who is
connected with us live and a lot of
spectators are present here at Fatima Teama
Grounds this is a great, a historic moment for
all the cricketers, for all the brokers here
ICICI Lombard proudly
presenting once again Brokers Premier
League Two to Six Season 3
Deepesh is here to binge
and there is a big responsibility now on Ramesh and Pratik to
set up a big partnership here.
Change in fielding here, two overs of play are
over.   The
power play ended here after two overs.   It
is mandatory to have a minimum of four fielders.
Inside the Circle.   We will
talk about four fielders.  Short cover,
point,
square leg and shot to third man.  This
is the four fielder inside circle.   The
square leg here has been sent slightly towards mid-wicket.
Short mid-wicket
and excellent boundaries are
rare.  Left arm
medium pace is a different thing on this pitch.
After left arm spin,
Om Sir left arm medium pace is also a
good bowling.  They affect.
Yes Mitesh,
as I said in the beginning, there are
three very good left arm bowlers in Anand Rathi.
Neeraj, as you saw Akash, the
next ball was a good ball from Deepesh.   Look, he
wanted to hit a full toss
in the off side but the ball turned in his hands
and went towards point for one run.
So, Dipesh gave a good start, giving away only three runs
in three balls,
one for 17. He says that
if there is a good economical bowling in the coming two overs, Anand Raj
United, then you can defend this target now.
Look at this and once there was a
slow one slow one delivery.   The
batsman was completely baffled.   It will be
very difficult to play on the leg side
because if you look at the distance, it is a very long
distance,
yes Mitesh is also far away and Deepesh
is very capable of taking the ball out.  I
told you that there are three left arm bowlers in this team.  The
next ball was a full toss.  As if he has
played it towards fine leg.  Beautiful
shot and gets a low full toss for four runs.
Yes, this time Deepesh will be a little angry with himself
because he hit a bad ball and hit it well on
fine leg for four and
now the Pink Panthers batsmen want that
such fireworks should continue.
Now Pratik Kadam is
a good batsman.
Ramesh is associated with him.   The
last ball of this over went
quite off course.
What happened Mitesh, that the four runs that came on the last ball
was a bit of a mindset of Deepesh
that this time I will bowl the ball a little outside the off stump
but it went off course.
22 runs, one wicket was a good ball.  It
was in a block hole.  The ball took the inside edge and
went towards fine leg.  The batsman ran for one run and was
satisfied with one run until the fielder caught the ball and threw it.   Yes.  The
over ends with one run.
One for 23 after three overs and need 40 from five overs.   Yes.
Eight runs per over.
Exactly eight overs,
Ramesh and Pratik are ready to win this match by scoring eight runs in each over but
Piyush Lodha is setting up the field there,
Captain of Anand Ra United
and he knows that in the coming two overs such
batting will have to be done, he will
try to defend this target, yes
once again Piyush has used a left arm bowler.
Neeraj
second over of his spell
I think Om sir I am also a leg
spinner.  Now I should also become a left arm spinner.
Yes Mitesh, we will also make a new innovation and a new beginning.   Exactly.
You also need a little practice.
Absolutely needed.  Played a lot of matches.  Three
matches were played here at Matima Ground
on leather ball.  Well it has been a good experience.   Yes, the
fielder made the judgment with great enthusiasm.
This makes the ball turn a little towards the
outside edge after hitting the shot.
Yes, the ball does spin a bit at point and third man.
If the fielder had
not been smart there, the ball could have turned and
gone for four runs.
But good fielding by Neeraj, next ball
good ball, very good keeping,
so far in this tournament, as per me, as long as
I am umpiring, the best
keeper
seems to be from Anand Rathi's team.
Collecting quite nice and clean.
Absolutely, even MS Dhoni was shocked there.
The way he kept
and the way he
is a keeper, it boosts the morale of the bowlers a lot.
Played with light hands towards point.  There is
no player.  The batsman ran for one run
but could not stop it from reaching four runs.
Powerful fantastic four.  With these four runs, the score
will increase to 28 and 35 runs are needed.  Now
in 27 balls,
Mitesh was a little surprised that
you have not kept point for the left arm bowler,
whose balls all come outside,
exactly here the same batsman saw it and
played a clever shot and we see that when a
left arm spinner bowls to a right
hand batsman, then Ravindra Jadeja and Yuvraj
Singh, you must have seen them keeping at point in international matches
and this time a big appeal
but safe,
very good keeping.
So we were talking about international cricket.
Ravindra Jadeja was a very good fielder.
I know that one moment.
He ran out Ricky Ponding.  The
throw was made from deep backward square leg at the
strikers end and
Krishna was the keeper.   He
strayed a little from the direction and could not escape the umpire's eyes.
Just like Krishna made Arjun win in Mahabharata.  We have to
see Krishna
trying his best,
you are absolutely right.  Anand Ra United
tried his best.  Pink Panthers try their best.
This time it has blown away.  Ball in the air is opportunity.  I will
grab it.
Fall of wicket, number two
wanted to play a big stroke but it went
into the hands of the long on fielder.
Sir,
yes, till now they have batsmen with the Pink Panthers.
Pratik Kadam is still
present at the Kaj.  Set is the batsman.  New
batsman
Rahul is also known for his big hits.  A
very
good batsman and
capable of hitting long shots.   Yes, you are
absolutely right.  Rahul Sawant is a big hitter.  You must have
heard the name Rahul but now you will
say you must have seen my exploits, the way I
bat now I have come in the middle order, a
big responsibility.
Yes Mitesh, next ball was a very
good ball from Neeraj, pushed lightly
towards cover and point for one run. The
over ended with seven runs given and a
wicket. Neeraj got
four overs. Two runs in 30 overs and need 33 runs in four overs. Runs
music.
New bowler Pushpak, let's
see what he does for his team
on the field. Rahul was
going with light steps.
Pushpak took a brilliant catch and
he has been promoted in the last over. Bowling, yes
Mitesh, let's see. Till now only three bowlers were
used, now four bowlers in eight overs. Let's
see what Pushpak does for his team.
Very good ball
but was
caught by Naushad Sir's eyes and the ball was wide.
This time he tried to hit big strokes
but could not do it from time to time.
Yes, Mitesh Pushpak may be
looking a bit light but he is able to
read the batsmen capable of turning the ball.
Yes, they say Murthy Lahanpan Par Kirti
Mahan,
yes see,
31 runs are needed on this ball, now 31 runs in 23 balls in 3.5 overs.
One big over Om sir and the match can turn around.
Excellent fielding here, the
long off fielder came in front of mid off.
30 runs needed.  3.4 coming
and this
ball is going too far outside off,
umpire Mr. Naushad Khan signals wide ball and says
29 runs are needed.
Excellent ball, wanted to connect but there was
no contact over the bat, if he had
connected it would have been a big hit,
medium pace slow variation is working a lot,
since yesterday we have seen many matches and now in the
quarter final,
this time the top edge backward region has been stopped
by the fielder, only a single,
absolutely here Krishna who is the wicketkeeper should
get the title of MSD.  Krishna The Untold
Story
and this time he has lifted the ball in the air, this is the opportunity.   The
umpire will check there.
A fantastic view of
Air India Airlines
42 That's the end of the over 40 for two after five overs
Need 23 runs
in three overs 23 runs in 18 balls Music to the Pink Panthers
40 for two after five overs
Coming to more special overs Left arm
spin into the attack and this time card away
Nicely
read it well Went on the back foot and
pushed it towards point for a run.
22 runs in 17 balls for Pink Panthers. Which
team will go to the semi-finals?
Howden has already entered the semi-finals.
They beat Pink Unilite Strikers
and the ball turned a bit but there were backup
fielders.  Shot The fielder at fine leg came at the
right time for backup towards third man Shot towards third man
and only one run will be scored
21 runs 16 balls here we go that's a good
shot good strike in the air just over the
fielder
big hit run ball now
I think Pink
Panthers can win this match easily even with one run but
Anand Rai United will not let the match go like this they will keep
looking for wickets they have definitely
blown the opportunity but no you
become spectators you are doing a
great job
eight runs are needed now only eight runs have won the match in 13 balls we need a
win
and this time Pink Panthers are in power
and there Pink Panthers the
noise meter has increased a bit here
this time the ball was in the block hole but
read it well it went well outside the off stump and two
runs will be taken here and they need a
big one six runs
six runs are needed in 12 balls so Pink Panthers
supporters make some noise
what a thing yes
but Anand Rai United now in these coming
overs a very crucial over of the match is coming
Up, wickets have to be taken, wickets
can help them here, we have to watch to win this match, the
tables can turn, anything can happen,
mean while music here we go,
six runs and
this time flick away nicely for a
single, all we need now is victory, Pink Panthers
need five runs
and good cricket has been
played here, Anand Ratan United have to be praised.
A big target has been blown away this time.  There
is a chance.  Oh, the catch is missed here.
Look, luck is giving you a chance.  Anything could have
turned around in this match but a catch was
dropped and four runs were needed.  Now will this be the winning
shot?  Pratik Kadam 26 15 balls two fours one
six and Rahul Sawant 12 eight balls one
six.   The
winning partnership has been 30.
Wanted to connect in 15 balls but got beaten. There is still a
chance. Four runs and nine balls left.
Deepesh will definitely be in search of a wicket.
This time he will hit hard. A
fielder is stationed in the mid-wicket area.  We will take only one run
here.
Just need three runs to get the semi-final
ticket.
That's high in the air
and take in something to cheer for Deepesh.
Something to do for Anand United.  Still we will
not let the match go like this.
Three runs needed in seven balls.  That's one more
wicket fall of Ping Panthers.
Three Runs from Seven Balls Music.
Three runs
Seven balls Hemant the captain
Good strike they are
looking for and sent back only a
single So only two more needed Six balls
for the Pink Panthers Ajooba Kamal Kuch Jadoo Karna Hui
Anand Ra United to defend this target
So six balls and two runs
Music
What a fantastic
environment here
at Fatima Grounds Vidya We are Mumbai
witnessing the exciting game of cricket
Oh what is this happening Something special
something magical from Anand Ra United They got one more
wicket Two runs now in five
balls
Wow
this is what happens
Never underestimate the power of
the common man.   No
team is to be underestimated.
What a man this is,
two runs in five balls,
Dil Dhakdhak Dhakdhak Dhakdhak
Prateek Bhandari,
if he collects here while throwing, he can get run out, the
score is at a level, one run is needed
in four balls, get
ready Pink Panthers team
and with this, the match has been won
and
so